http://coffeeam.com/pages/privacy-policy

Coffee RegularGourmet CoffeeSingle-origin CoffeeFlavored CoffeeOrganic CoffeeCoffee BlendsEspressoRegularFair Trade CoffeeMicro-Lot CoffeeSingle Serve Coffee CupsGreen CoffeeCoffees for a CauseDecafDecaf Single-Origin CoffeeDecaf Organic CoffeeDecaf EspressoDecaf Coffee BlendsFlavored Decaf CoffeeSingle-Origin CoffeeTea Gourmet TeaGourmet TeaLoose LeafHerbal TeaChaiGourmet TeaFlavored TeasBag TeaTisaneLoose Leaf TeaFlavorings & Mixes Flavorings & MixesFlavorings & MixesGourmet Flavoring PowderCoffee SyrupCoffee SauceFlavorings & MixesFrappe & Latte MixReal Fruit Smoothie MixHot Cocoa MixMonin Zero Calorie Natural Flavor SyrupsCoffee SyrupSPECIALS $6 Half PoundsBlack FridayCorporate GiftsCheck Out:Fall FavoritesLBBCThanksgiving CoffeesCoffee Pods50% OffFundraisingReward ProgramGift Sets Holidays:ThanksgivingChristmasValentine's DayShop by HolidayGift SetsGift SetsCorporate GiftsChocolate Coffee GiftsNew Gift SetsGift CardsGift SetsCoffee SamplersCoffee Gift SetsTea Gift SetsTortuga Rum CakeCoffee ClubSeasonal Coffee & Tea GiftsGift CardsAccessories AccessoriesAccessoriesHome EquipmentCommercial Coffee BrewersCommercial Espresso MachinesCommercial Coffee GrindersBarista toolsEquipment Cleaning ProductsBeverage DispensersAccessoriesTea Equipment & AccessoriesBlendersCoffee AirpotsDecanters & Coffee PotsFiltersAccessoriesWarming PlatesCoffee ServersCoffee Stands & RacksHot Water DispensersOne Cup Coffee MakersHome EquipmentWholesale WholesaleCafe Equipment PackagesPrivate Label ProgramRecipes & Menu ItemsWholesale CoffeeWholesale TeaWholesaleWholesale Coffee SauceWholesale Coffee SyrupWholesale Smoothie MixWholesale Frappe MixWholesale Hot Cocoa MixGourmet Flavoring PowderWholesaleTrending What's TrendingWhat's TrendingBest SellersTop Rated Single Origin CoffeeTop Rated Organic CoffeeTop Rated Flavored CoffeeNEW at CoffeeAM!What's TrendingTop Rated Coffee BlendsTop Rated Decaf CoffeeTop Rated Gourmet TeasTop Rated Coffee & Tea GiftsCafe@HomeWhat's TrendingFall FavoritesWinter SelectionsSpring SelectionsSummer ClassicsWhat's Trending
Skip to content
Home
Privacy Policy
Updated December 2019 CoffeeAM Privacy Policy CoffeeAM understands that visitors to their site may be concerned about information that we collect from them as well as how we use this information; this Privacy Policy addresses such concerns. Information We Collect In offering our services to you, we collect information from you that you choose to provide to us through the website, and certain information by automated means, as further described below. We may also engage third party analytics services providers such as Google Analytics in order to better understand your use of our website.  Information You Provide to Us When you make a purchase from our online store, you can opt to check out over the phone or via our secure checkout. Either option will require that you provide us with certain personal information like your email address, mailing and billing address, contact information, as well as your credit card information. If you choose to checkout via our online store, we will collect your name, billing and shipping information, and credit card information in order to process your order. In accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), we do not intentionally collect information from children under 13 years of age.Information We Collect by Automated Means There are certain types of information that we collect by automated means. Here are some examples of such information: the number of users who have visited the website, the pages that they have viewed, and IP addresses. We collect this information solely for the purpose of improving our website, as well as coming up with ways to improve user experience. We collect some of this information through the use of "cookies."  In order to provide a better web experience for visitors, we use cookies, which are small text files that are able to recognize repeat visitors. Cookies simply help us identify your browsing and purchasing behavior on our site so that we can feature products that are of interest to you. We also use cookies to keep items in your shopping card while you continue to shop. However, you can choose to change the settings on your browser so that these features are blocked. Our website may use Google Analytics, a web analysis service provided by Google, in order to better understand your use of our website and how we can improve them. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit a website, what pages you visit when you do so, and what other website you used prior to coming to such website. Google Analytics collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit a website, rather than your name or other identifying information. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with your personal information. Although Google Analytics plants a permanent cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit a website, the cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to our website is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of Use and the Google Privacy Policy. Google utilizes the data collected to track and examine the use of the our website, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services. Google may use the data collected on our website to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. To more fully understand how Google may use the data it collects on the our website, please review “How Google Uses Information From Sites Or Apps That Use Our Services,” (located here or any successor URL). How We Use and Share This Information  The information that we collect is used solely by CoffeeAM and subsidiaries and will not be shared with other entities who are not involved in the operation of our business and related services. We may share personally identifiable information with third parties as permitted by applicable laws, including: (i) when sharing of information is required to operate the site; for example, to process a credit or debit card transaction, or (ii) if the law requires it. Security We take commercially reasonable measures to secure and protect information transmitted via our website. Nevertheless, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee that information that users of our website transmit will be totally secure.  Visiting The Website From Outside The United States If you are visiting our website from outside of the United States of America, please be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored or processed in the United States, where our servers are located and our central database is operated. The data protection and other laws of the United States and other countries might not be as comprehensive as those in your country, but please be assured that we take steps to protect your privacy. By using any portion of the Website, you understand and consent to the transfer of your information to our facilities in the United States and those third parties with whom we share it as described in this Privacy Policy. Email Marketing  For interested customers, we provide the opportunity of receiving emails for promotional offers. Customers can always unsubscribe from our email campaigns if they wish to, and they can do so without any assistance from us. We may also email you to remind you when you have initiated but not completed a transaction in our online shopping card if you have provided us your email address as a part of the checkout process.  Updates to Our Privacy Policy  At our discretion, we can choose to update this Privacy Policy without any prior notice to you. This may be done from time to time to reflect changes in how we handle information. We will inform you of this by indicating at the top left corner of this policy the month and year when it was last updated. Contact Us Thank you for visiting our site. If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, feel free to contact us at: CoffeeAM, Inc.ATTN: Customer Relations12230 Cumming HwyCanton, GA 301151-800-803-7774Email: CustomerRelations@coffeeam.com
Join our mailing list
Get in the Grind with Our Latest News, Special Offers and Coupons!
Added to your cart:
(-)
Cart subtotal
